<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RoadSide Asst</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Phone No.</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_dash_board">DashBoardActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="txt1">Roadside Assistance representatives are standing by 24/7 to assist you. Should you require further assistance you need
    to cancel your roadside assistance request, please contact Roadside Assistance using the button below.
    </string>
    <string name="txt2">To Better serve you, specialists are available to take your call from
        9 AM to 9 PM Indian Standard Time(+5:30 GMT),Monday through Saturday.</string>
    <string name="txt3">The RSA (Roadside Assistance) mobile application is a free, easy to use mobile resoure connecting you with Roadside Assistance at touch of a button.</string>
    <string name="eula">
        End-User License Agreement ("Agreement"):
Last updated: July 14, 2016
Please read this End-User License Agreement ("Agreement") carefully before clicking the "I Agree" button, downloading or using RSA ("Application").
By clicking the "I Agree" button, downloading or using the Application, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
This Agreement is a legal agreement between you (either an individual or a single entity) and RSA and it governs your use of the Application made available to you by RSA.
If you do not agree to the terms of this Agreement, do not click on the "I Agree" button and do not download or use the Application.
The Application is licensed, not sold, to you by RSA for use strictly in accordance with the terms of this Agreement.
License
RSA grants you a revocable, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited license to download, install and use the Application solely for your personal, non-commercial purposes strictly in accordance with the terms of this Agreement.


    </string>

</resources>
